PHAM TRUONG HUNG

Personal details:

Phone: 01222474842

Email: truonghungit@gmail.com

DOB: 20 - 04 - 1992

Address: 436 Truong Chinh, 13th Ward, Tan Binh District, Ho Chi Minh City, Vietnam

Summary

With more than three year of experiences in software development, special web application, I can understand well the software life cycle include business analysis, design, code and test, especially for projects in Dot Net technology. I am eager to learn new things, always try my best to get the job done.

Technical Proficiencies

- Dot Net Framework, WPF, LinQ in C#.
- ASP.NET MVC.
- Web Service, RESTful, web API, Single Page Application technology.
- HTML, LESS/CSS-3, JavaScript, jQuery, Bootstrap, Requires JS, Angular JS, React JS...
- Entity Framework for ORM
- MS SQL Server, MySQL

Professional Experience

Hyrecar Project

Web Development – Eztek Software Company 8/2016 – Present.

Hyrecar is a website allow user listing your car and driver rent a car for Uber & Lyft http://hyrecar.com/

My role and responsibilities were as follows:

• Code and testing.

Technologies Utilized:

- PHP, MySQL
- HTML, CSS, LESS, JavaScript
- Single Page Application with AngularJS
- Gulp Grunt.

BBA Logistics Project

Web Development – Eztek Software Company 5/2016 – 10/2016

BBA Logistics Pty Ltd (BBA) was founded by identifying a gap in the freight & logistics market, where the current landscape of technology solutions lacked comprehensive, simple to use functionality. BBA was born to provide businesses the ability to solve this problem as well as identifying a unique logistics solution, named break bulk, which the software automates for customers both domestically and internationally. http://dashboard.bbalogistics.com.au/

My role and responsibilities were as follows:

- Implement front-end.
- Testing

Technologies Utilized:

- HTML, CSS, LESS, JavaScript
- Single Page Application with AngularJS
- Webpack

Tyto Project

Web Development – Eztek Software Company 01/2016 – 5/2016

Tyto is a fun, gamified to-do list & tasking engine. Tyto feels as easy as a personal to-do app, but it's power shines in teams. http://www.tyto.me

My role and responsibilities were as follows:

- Implement front-end.
- Testing

Technologies Utilized:

- HTML, CSS, LESS, Javascript, Angular material
- Single Page Application with AngularJS
- Testing with Jasmine
- Node Js, Grunt task runner

KinhDo Project

Web Development – Eztek Software Company 5/2015 – 02/2016

This a web application for managing content. Show product and news in client view Team of 3 developers, works with SCRUM methodology,

http://buaantienloi.kinhdo.vn

My role and responsibilities were as follows:

- Implement front-end layout
- Implement Server side
- Testing

Technologies Utilized:

- ASP.NET MVC-5, .Net Framework, Entity Framework.
- HTML, CSS, LESS, Javascript, jQuery, Ajax, Bootstrap
- Single Page Application AngularJS

SupportOn Project

Web Development – Eztek Software Company 1/2015 – 6/2016

SupportOn is a customer service based on web application. The system manages Agents belong to companies who are using this system to consult, support clients. System provide functionalities like: schedule working time, mail client, client and agent web chat, calling, acknowledgement,...

My role and responsibilities were as follows:

- Implement front-end.
- Testing

Technologies Utilized:

- Spring framework, Spring security Oauth2, Spring Data, Jersey REST API, Atmosphere Framework, Quart Scheduler, Smack API
- HTML, CSS, LESS, JavaScript, jQuery, Ajax, Bootstrap
- Openfire Server, Twillio, MySql Server, Tomcat 7
- Single Page Application with RequireJS, AngularJS

Car Finding E-Commerce System

Web Development – Eztek Software Company 6/2014 – 12/2014

This is an e-commerce website which provides functionalities for sellers to promote cars that they want to sell, and let buyers find the most suitable car for them, providing sellers contact information. Team of 6 developers, working on SCRUM methodology, JIRA (www.atlassian.net) for tasks management and GIT (www.bitbucket.org) source control.

My role and responsibilities were as follows:

- Create database
- Coding, Test

Technologies Utilized:

- ASP.NET MVC5, WebAPI, .Net Framework, Entity Framework Code First, LinQ
- HTML, CSS, LESS, JavaScript, jQuery, Bootstrap
- MS SQL Server 2012, using Code-First Migration technique to control database migration between team members.
- Single Page Application with RequireJS, AngularJS

HTML5 Interactive House Decorate Website

Web Development – Eztek Software Company 1/2014 – 6/2014

This project is to do a website allowing the users to decorate the bath rooms, kitchen rooms themselves by creating tiles on the walls and floor. The website uses HTML5 canvas and FabricJS library for creating interactive UI, allows drawing, moving, and resizing tiles.

My role and responsibilities were as follows:

• Coding and Test

Technologies Utilized:

- HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Ajax, Bootstrap
- Fabric JavaScript Library

Education

Sai Gon University, Ho Chi Minh City, Vietnam 2010 – 2015